[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Eating carrots can improve a persons night vision.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Indiana Jones friend, who flies a seaplane in Raiders of the Lost Ark, has a pet snake. Name this character and his pet.", "correct_answer": "Jock and Reggie", "incorrect_answers": ["John and Sam", "Jake and Snake", "George and Randy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the largest European island, and the ninth-largest island on the planet.", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Sicily", "Sardinia", "Cyprus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Simply Red is a British band. The bands name is related to this soccer team.", "correct_answer": "Manchester United", "incorrect_answers": ["Arsenal", "Liverpool", "Middlesbrough"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This country, situated in North Europe, has almost 200 000 lakes - more than any other country in the world.", "correct_answer": "Finland", "incorrect_answers": ["Sweden", "The Netherlands", "Georgia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actors was not a student of Stella Adler?", "correct_answer": "Richard Dreyfuss", "incorrect_answers": ["Michael  Imperioli", "Vincent DOnoffrio", "Mark Ruffalo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What country employs the blue color as its national sports color, as it denotes secularism?", "correct_answer": "India", "incorrect_answers": ["South Korea", "Spain", "Italy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actors played a role in the 1989 movie Pink Cadillac?", "correct_answer": "Jim Carrey", "incorrect_answers": ["Eddie Murphy", "Jack Black", "Michael Douglas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "She directed Desperately Seeking Susan as well as  some episodes of Sex and The City and Now and Again. Her mother wrote The Boynton Beach Bereavement Club.", "correct_answer": "Susan Seidelman", "incorrect_answers": ["Nora Ephron", "Ida Lupino", "Lee Grant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is a new type of massage, introduced in 1990 by Hemi Hoani Fox. It originates from the Hawaiian Lomi-Lomi Nui dance and is believed to increase the energy flow within the body and mind.", "correct_answer": "MA-URI massage", "incorrect_answers": ["Zhi Ya massage", "Tui Na massage", "Shiatsu"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the average number of sweat glands in the skin per square inch (6.5cm\u00b2)?", "correct_answer": "650", "incorrect_answers": ["1100", "3000", "125"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor was a founding member of Lee Strasbergs Actors Studio. He became famous as District Attorney Adam Schiff, a part he played for ten seasons on a successful NBC drama series.", "correct_answer": "Steven Hill", "incorrect_answers": ["Dennis Farina", "Tom Bosley", "Roy Thinnes"]}]